

ATIKAH AZMI SIREGAR

+62 823-6353-6685 | atikahazmisiregar@gmail.com | https://linkedin.com/in/atikahasrg/ | https://atikahazmisiregar.netlify.app/

Kabupaten Langkat, Sumatera Utara

Fresh Graduate of Industrial Engineering at Malikussaleh University in 2022, GPA 3,74. Have internship experience in Marketing Insurance and State Electricity Company. Self-motivated to always learn, target-oriented and adaptable. I'm interested in Management, Analysis, Digital and Technology.

Work Experiences

BPJS Kesehatan - Lhokseumawe, Indonesia

Feb 2022 - Jul 2022

Relationship Officer

- Mastered product knowledge, management and marketing company's product (JKN-KIS)
- · Marketed and managed BPJS Kesehatan's service through canvassing or telemarketing
- Collecting and updating participants deactivation submission data from Edabu application
- · Capable manage BPJS sites for registration, termination and revision of BPJS accounts
- Develop easy-to-understand communication, solved customer's question and problems directly
- Succeeded increase participants satisfication by 45-55% of JKN-KIS BPJS Kesehatan's program at Malikussaleh University

PT. Indonesia Power PLTU - Sumatera Utara, Indonesia

Jul 2021 - Aug 2021

Process Analyst Intern

- · Mastered company's production process: water, fuel and steam cycle
- Analyzed and quantified the effectiveness of belt conveyor as coal transporter using Overall Equipment Effectiveness & Failure Mode and Effect Analysis Method.
- Presented my result analysis and Suggested improvements for the company's progress.

Education Level

Malikussaleh University - Lhokseumawe, Indonesia

Sep 2018 - Aug 2022

Bachelor Degree in Industrial Engineering, 3.74/4.00

- Alumni MSIB Kampus Merdeka Batch 1 & , BEM FT Unimal's Mentor, BEM Unimal's Teacher Volunteer, Entrepreneurship Student Program: Rempah Drink
- Final Project: Analyzed Service Quality of BPJS Kesehatan's Mobile JKN Application Using the Service Quality (Servqual) Method

Alterra Academy - Indonesia

Aug 2021 - Jan 2022

Certificate in Full Stack Engineering

- Mastered Frontend Web Engineering (React Development) use React Js. and Backend Engineering (REST API Development).
- UI/UX Design use Figma & Managed Code use GitHub.
- Capstone Project: Hospital Management System as Frontend Engineer & UI/UX Design.

Progate - Indonesia Mar 2023 - Apr 2023

Certificate in Frontend Development

- · Mastered Frontend Development use HTML&CSS, JavaScript and Git
- Complete project team to build Pet Shop Website use HTML&CSS, JavaScript
- Final Project: Calculator Website

Sinergi Tuntas Solusi - Indonesia

Mar 2022 -

Certificate in Odoo Developer

- · Mastered inventory knowledge
- Mastered Odoo ERP syste and completed odoo projects
- Final project: Developed Odoo ERP systems for client (Apotek Sinergi) as Leader and Project Manager

Organisational Experience

MSIB Kampus Merdeka - Indonesia

Feb 2022 - Aug 2022

Chief of Tribe BPJS Kesehatan

- Succeeded manage team of 113 BPJS Kesehatan's program participants
- · Coordinated Kampus Merdeka's team with company and program participants.
- · Organized participants data and documents.
- Checked and ensured data and documents of program participants meet the requirements for distribursing salary

Member of Education and Social Division

- Planned and organized seminars or training events for Industrial Engineering students
- · Responsible for the implementation and failure of seminars or training activities
- · Cooperate with other divisions in the success of Himpunan's events

Skills, Achievements & Other Experience

- Soft Skills: Team Work, Leadership, Target-oriented, Time Management, Critical Thinking
- Hard Skills: Microsoft Office, Google Work Space, Marketing Management, Data Management, SQL, Odoo ERP, Canva, Vs Code
- · Achievements (2022): TOEFL Score: 453 Certified by Language Center Malikussaleh University
- Webinars Attended (2022): Digital Marketing Festival by Rakamin Academy
- Webinars Attended (2022): Digital Marekting VIX by Rakamin Academy
- Webinars Attended (2022): Product and Business Developer VIX